Q.
IN WHAT YEAR DID COLUMBUS
DISCOVER THE "NEW WORLD"?
THE CORRECT ANSWER
WILL OPEN THE LOCK.
JOJO'S BIZARRE ADVENTURE
DIAMOND IS UNBREAKABLE
These faceless gazes pass by one another
A wound to the heart changes our everyday
Encounters without boundaries
The bizarre is our normal U-yeh
These ordinary mornings,
we're laughing on the surface
Mysteries drawn to each other,
identity still unknown
Without a heads up,
it's quietly lurking somewhere in this town
Although we bicker and complain
In the end, we celebrate
Dancing through the everyday
Crazy Noisy Bizarre Town
EPISODE 9
YUKAKO YAMAGISHI
FALLS IN LOVE, PART 2
BEEP BEEP BEEP
I HATE YOU
REVERB
FWOOSH
CROWN
DOGON
BOING
MORIOH LANDMARK 2
CAPE BOING
DIRECTIONS: ASK A LOCAL FISHERMAN
FOR "CAPE BOING,"
AND HE WILL RESPOND IN KIND
BY TAKING YOU THERE BY BOAT.
ENGLISH EXAM ANSWER SHEET
TEST 3 KOICHI HIROSE
EPISODE 10
LET'S GO EAT SOME ITALIAN FOOD